Guide to the New York State AFL-CIO Records WAG.031
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Inventory, 1
  - Officers, Jaffe, Ludwig (LJ): Correspondence 1956-1981 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Officers, Jaffe, Ludwig (LJ): Correspondence Personal, 1954-1956 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Officers, Jaffe, Ludwig (LJ): Speeches, Statements, 1977-1979 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Officers, Murphy, Joseph P.: Correspondence, 1956-1964 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Officers, Murphy, Joseph P.: Notes, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Press Releases: 1945-1954 NYCIO (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases: 1955-1958 NYCIO (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases: 1959 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases: 1960-1964 (selected) (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases: 1969-1970, Jan-May 1975, 1975 (selected), 1969-1970; 1975 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases: 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases: 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Press Releases: 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Press Releases: 1978-1979, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Printed Material: CIO Reporter, 1945-1957 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Printed Material: New York State AFL-CIO News, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Printed Material: Legislative Bulletin, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Public Relations: Press Contact lists, 1952-1957 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Resumes: Jose Ramos, Florence Dreizen Judicial appointments, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Resumes: 1978-1981 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Resumes: 1982 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Resumes: 1983 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.55A-S.728 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S. 139 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S1001F NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S1002B-S1457 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.1509-S.1999 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.2001-S.2465 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.2503A-S.2906 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.3010-S.3540A NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.3247A NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.3555-S.3994 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.4016-S.4586 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.4202B NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.4606A-S.4908 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.5073A-S.5446 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.558-S.5944 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.6024A-S.6250 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.6310B-S.6579 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.6331-S.6911 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.7036-S.7396 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.7495-S.7985B NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.8207-S.8584 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.8723-S.8952 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.9066-S.9563 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.9618-S.9920 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.10065-S.10532 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Legislation: 1975-1976 S.10605-S.10738 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 A.101A-A.1938 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 A.2293-A.2972 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 A.3282-A.4916 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 A.5030-A.5937B NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 A.6143A-A.7947C NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 A.8043-A.8182 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 A.8111 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 A.9016-A.9295 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 A.10167-A.11718 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 A.12186-A.13146 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.9A-S.142 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.219A-S.395 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.405-S.574 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S3654-S.778 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.863-S.1096 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.1128-S.1381 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978S.1401-S.1660 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.1711-S.1983 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.2077-S.2387 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.2441A-S.2987 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.3032A-S.3498 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.3526-S.3959 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.4065A-S.4545A NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.4631A-S.4950A NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.5053-S.5493 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.5517-S.5969 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.6019A-S.6376 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.6043B NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.6502-S.6655 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.6706A NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978S.6706-S.6934 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.6927 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.7000-S.7292 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.7389-S.7694 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978S.7744-S.7975 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978S.8058A-S.8319 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.8470A-S.8825 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.9129A-S.9367 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.9428-S.9882A NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.10120-S.10306 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 S.10028-S.10429 NYS AFL-CIO Positions (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 Assembly Labor Comm. Agendas (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 Assembly Labor Comm. Agendas (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 Assembly Labor Comm. Agendas (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 Assembly Labor Comm. Agendas (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 Assembly Labor Comm. Agendas (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 Assembly Labor Comm. Agendas (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 Assembly Labor Comm. Agendas (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: 1977-1978 Assembly Labor Comm. Agendas (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - 1976 Session: Aggregate Trust Fund (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - 1976 Session: Budget NYS (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - 1976 Session: COPE (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - 1976 Session: Correspondence handled by Albany office (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - 1976 Session: Economic Impact Statements (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - 1976 Session: NYS AFL-CIO Constitutional Convention (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - 1976 Session: Political Endorsements (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - 1976 Session: Voting Record (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - 1976 Session: Workers Comp Legislative Efforts (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - 1977 Session: COPE (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - 1977 Session: Correspondence handled by Albany office, Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - 1977 Session: Correspondence handled by Albany office, Jul-Dec 1977 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - 1978 Session: Domestic International Banking Facilities (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - 1978 Session: COPE (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - 1978 Session: Correspondence handled by Albany office, Jan-Mar 1978 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - 1978 Session: Correspondence handled by Albany office, Apr-Jun 1978 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - 1978 Session: Correspondence handled by Albany office, Jul-Dec 1978 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - 1978 Session: Elections (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - 1978 Session: Environmental Quality Act (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - 1978 Session: NYS AFL-CIO Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - 1978 Session: Unions, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - 1978 Session: Unions, 1975-1978 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - 1978 Session: Unions, 1976; 1978 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - 1978 Session: Unions, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - 1978 Session: Unions, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - 1978 Session: Unions (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - 1978 Session: Unions, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - 1978 Session: Unions, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - 1978 Session: Unions, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - 1978 Session: Unions, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - 1978 Session: Unions (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - 1978 Session: Unions, 1976-1978 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - 1978 Session: Unions (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - 1978 Session: Unions, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - 1978 Session: Voting Record, 1975-1978 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - 1978 Session: Voting Record (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - 1978 Session: Westway (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - 1978 Session: Workers Comp (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Mondale-Ferraro Campaign: Election Materials, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Invoices, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Invoices, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Labor Delegates, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - School of Education of the State University of NY of Albany: Reception for Al Shanker & Fred Hechinger, Sep 21 1984 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - WNY PAC, Sep 24 1984 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Cornell University at NYSUT, Sep 25 1984 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Executive Council and Labor Leaders, Sep 26 1984 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Univ., ILR Adv. Committee Meeting, Sep 28 1984 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - NYSUT Rochester: Reg. Office Leadership Conference, Sep 30 1984 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - COPE Meeting: International Reps., Oct 3 1984 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - American Management Assoc. Meeting, Oct 8-10 1984 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - NYSUT SRP Conference, Oct 12-14 1984 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - OPEIU: Loc. 153 Shop Stewards Meeting, Oct 13 1984 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Lane Kirkland Rally, Oct 14 1984 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - WNY PAC / NYSUT Mondale/Ferraro Rally, Oct 15 1984 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Tri-County Labor Council, Oct 16 1984 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Minnesota Fed. of Teachers, Oct 18 1964 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Job Training Partnership Council Testimony, Oct 22 1984 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - WNY Educational Conf., Oct 22 1984 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Steelworkers Meeting, Oct 25 1984 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Syracuse Teachers Association, Oct 26 1984 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - NYSUT: Board Meeting, Oct 29 1984 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Rally for Mondale, Oct 31 1984 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Sheet Metal Workers Rally, Nov 1 1984 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Breakfast with Mondale, Nov 1 1984 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting, Nov 8 1984 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Cornell Labor Studies Alumni Association, Nov 14 1984 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Greater Glens Falls Central Labor Council, Nov 16 1984 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Cornell ILR School, Nov 17 1984 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Cornell: Labor Forum, Nov 20 1984 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Friends of Mario Cuomo, Nov 26 1984 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Labor Heritage Week, UFT, Nov 27 1984 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Northeast AFL-CIO Council Meeting, Nov 28-29 1984 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Legislative Issues Conference, Nov 30 1984 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Kemp Voting Record, undated (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Voter Registration Project, undated (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Labor for Lundine Committee, undated (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - 1984 Report to COPE Advisory Committee (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - 1984 Report to COPE Advisory Committee (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - 1984 Report to COPE Advisory Committee (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Mondale/Ferraro Campaign, undated (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Mondale/Ferraro Campaign, undated (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Mondale/Ferraro Campaign, undated (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Council COPE Directors, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Albany Central Labor Council, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Auburn Central Labor Council, 1979-1983 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Bradford-Tioga Central Labor Council, 1977-1981 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Broome County Labor Council, 1978-1984 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Buffalo Labor Council, 1978-1985 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Cattoragaugus / Alleghany Labor Council, 1978-1983 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Central NY Labor Council, 1977-1984 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Dunkirk Labor Council, 1978-1984 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Dutchess County Organizing Comm., 1980-1982 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Genesee / Wyoming Labor Council, 1977-1984 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Glens Falls Labor Council, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Upper Hudson Area Council, 1977-1986 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Jamestown Area Council, 1978; 1984 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Jefferson / Lewis / St. Lawrence Labor Council, 1977-1984 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Long Island Labor Council, 1978-1982 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: NYC Central Labor Council, 1979-1984 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Niagaral Orleans Labor Council, 1978-1984 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Northeast Central Labor Council, 1978-1983 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Orange County Central Labor Council, 1981-1985 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Oswego County Labor Council, 1977-1983 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Peekskill Central Labor Council, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Rochester Labor Council, 1977-1985 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Rockland County Labor Council, 1978-1984 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Saratoga County Labor Council, 1978-1982 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Schenectady Area Labor Council, 1978-1983 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Syracuse Area Labor Council, 1978-1984 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Tri-County Labor Council, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Troy Area Labor Council, 1978-1982 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - NYS Central Labor Council Correspondence: Westchester / Putnam labor Council, 1979-1984 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - American Labor Studies, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - White House Conference on Productivity, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - AFT Standing Committee on Vocational Education, 1980-1982 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Educare, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Education Update, 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Education: Whats Right, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Discipline, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Computers in Education, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Coleman Report, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1974-1977 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Community Education, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Class Size, 1973; 1976 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Copyright Laws, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Civil Rights, 1974-1977 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Censorship, 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Casino Gambling, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Campaign Material, undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - School Representatives: Training Course, undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Industry / Economics: Articles, undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Bilingualism, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Bottom Line, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Builders, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Resolution for Vocational Education Committee (NYSUT), Jul 1 1982 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Executive Council Meeting, Mar 27 1984 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Endorsements, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Environment, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - 1984 Hearing Testimony (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Insurance Association, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Job Training, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Kills, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Labor Committee, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Labor Department Program Bills, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Laws of 1984 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Old Memos, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - RWDSU Local 1199, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Resolutions, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Service Employees, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Sheet Metal Workers 1984 Senate Agendas (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - State Senate, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Taxi Drivers, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Teachers, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Transport Workers, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Tunnel Workers, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - VAW, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - 1984 of + CW (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - United Transportation Workers (Railroad Unions), 1984 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Union Busting, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Water Tunnel, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - West Way, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Worker Cooperatives, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Youth Employment, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Legislative Session S.10074: Lack, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Session S.10080: Goodhue, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Session A.11938: Jacobs, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Session S.10086: Rules, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Session S.10102: Lack, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Session A.11958: Rules, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Session S.10126: Schermerhorn, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Session A.11975: Rules, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Session S.10129: Flynn, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Session A.11835: Rules, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Legislative Session S.10135: Rules, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Session A.282: McCabe, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Legislative Session A.304: Robach, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Legislative Session A.343: Lafayette, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Legislative Session A.436: Lipschutz, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Legislative Session A.663: DAndrea, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Legislative Session A.825: Eve, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Legislative Session A.846: Hoblock, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Legislative Session A.853: Koppell, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Legislative Session A.1148: Butler, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Legislative Session A.1450: Eve, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Legislative Session A.1503: Gottfried, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Legislative Session A.1712B: Feldman, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Legislative Session A.1725: Gottfried, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Legislative Session A.1770: Orazio, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Legislative Session A.2042A: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Legislative Session A.2127A: Barbaro, Madison, et al., 1984 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Legislative Session A.2129B: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Legislative Session A.2136: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Legislative Session A.2137: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Legislative Session A.2908: Seminerio, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Legislative Session A.2500: Eve, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Legislative Session A.3057: Seminerio, et al., 1984 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Legislative Session A.3059: Seminerio, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Legislative Session A.3100: Sullivan, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Legislative Session A.3159B: Levy, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Legislative Session A.3180A: Passannante, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Legislative Session A.3211D: Brodsky, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Legislative Session A.3274: Dugan, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Legislative Session A.3275: Dugan, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Legislative Session A.3418: P. Sullivan, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Legislative Session A.3546: Saland, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Legislative Session A.3547: Schimminger, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Legislative Session A.3585: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Legislative Session A.3775: Pilliterre, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Legislative Session A.4020: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Legislative Session A.4736: Onzio, Butler, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Legislative Session A.4945: Engel, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Legislative Session A.4987: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Legislative Session A.5158A: Lentol, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Legislative Session A.5213: Nadler, et al., 1984 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Legislative Session A.5557: Engel, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - Legislative Session A.5558: Engel, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Legislative Session A.5562: Kuhl, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Legislative Session A.5569: Nadler, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - Legislative Session A.5580: Sanders, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - Legislative Session A.5875: Rules Committee, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - Legislative Session A.6146A: Barbaro, et al., 1984 (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - Legislative Session A.6153: Marchisell, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - Legislative Session A.6969: Fink, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - Legislative Session A.7232A: Tallon, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 61)
  - Legislative Session A.7298: Bragman, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 62)
  - Legislative Session A.7312: Brodsky, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 63)
  - Legislative Session A.7578: Rules Committee, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 64)
  - Legislative Session A.8410: Miller, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 65)
  - Legislative Session A.8442: Spano, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 66)
  - Legislative Session A.8719: Brodsky, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 67)
  - Legislative Session A.8724: Ferris, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 68)
  - Legislative Session A.8865: Pillitterre, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 69)
  - Legislative Session A.9218A: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 70)
  - Legislative Session A.9231: Madison, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 71)
  - Legislative Session A.9262: Mealy, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 72)
  - Legislative Session A.9323: Daniels, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 73)
  - Legislative Session A.9357: Orazio, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 74)
  - Legislative Session A.9358: Eve, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 75)
  - Legislative Session A.9435: Fink, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 76)
  - Legislative Session A.9520: Vitaliano, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 77)
  - Legislative Session A.9527: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 78)
  - Legislative Session A.9528: Gorski, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 79)
  - Legislative Session A.9538: Sanders, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 80)
  - Legislative Session A.9554: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 81)
  - Legislative Session A.9555: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 82)